{
    "subject": "resource/Madame_Butterfly_(1915_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Madame Butterfly is a 1915 silent film directed by Sidney Olcott. The film is based upon a John Luther Long novel and the opera Madama Butterfly.",
    "human_readable": "Madame Butterfly is a 1915 silent film directed by Sidney Olcott, based on a John Luther Long novel and the opera Madama Butterfly.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8989139795303345,
            "question": "Who directed the silent film *Madame Butterfly*?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6751407384872437,
            "question": "On what literary work is the film *Madame Butterfly* based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6008084416389465,
            "question": "What is the name of the opera connected to the film *Madame Butterfly*?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5781228542327881,
            "question": "What type of film was *Madame Butterfly*?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.558940589427948,
            "question": "What year was the film *Madame Butterfly* released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5348178744316101,
            "question": "Who wrote the novel that inspired the film *Madame Butterfly*?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3218659460544586,
            "question": "What genre does the source material for *Madame Butterfly* likely belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3173792064189911,
            "question": "Is there a connection between the film and an opera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2411133199930191,
            "question": "What could be some common themes found in both films and operas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23441430926322937,
            "question": "Would you expect a silent film to have dialogue?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Madame Butterfly is a 1915 silent film directed by Sidney Olcott, based on a John Luther Long novel and the opera Madama Butterfly.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7241_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What could be some common themes found in both films and operas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7241_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between the film and an opera?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7241_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does the source material for *Madame Butterfly* likely belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7241_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7241_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7241_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7241_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7241_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7241_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7241_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7241_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7241_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7241_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7241_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents indicate that there were multiple adaptations of \"Madame Butterfly,\" including one from 1932 directed by Marion Gering, but do not provide information to confirm it as a 1915 silent film directed by Sidney Olcott. Additionally, while the novel and opera are mentioned, there is no specific confirmation linking them in this exact way or mentioning Sidney Olcott as the director for that year."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is a 1915 film, but it was directed by Marion Gering, not Sidney Olcott.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that \"Madame Butterfly (1915)\" is not a film, but supposedly based on the original John Luther Long book. Furthermore, it mentions two different films of Madame Butterfly from 1915 and 1932 directed by Sidney Olcott and Marion Gering respectively. Therefore, there was no 1915 silent film directed by Sidney Olcott titled or based on Madame Butterfly.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}